<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Xunyun Liu - PhD(Melb)</title>
    <link>https://xunyunliu.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Xunyun Liu - PhD(Melb)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Xunyun Liu</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://xunyunliu.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sample Questions on Distribtued Systems</title>
      <link>https://xunyunliu.github.io/post/samepledsquestions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 10:25:19 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xunyunliu.github.io/post/samepledsquestions/</guid>
      <description>Download the slide in pdf format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Message Broadcaster Demo for Distributed Systems</title>
      <link>https://xunyunliu.github.io/post/messagebroadcaster/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 10:25:19 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xunyunliu.github.io/post/messagebroadcaster/</guid>
      <description>A message broadcaster implemented in a client-server architecture to demonstrate the use of multi-threading and socket communication in Java.
 Clients read server IP/port from config file Clients establish a TCP connection with the server Users type a message using the console, the client sends it to the server, the server broadcasts that message to all clients currently connected (including the sending client) and the clients display the message to the user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install Sogou input on Ubuntu 16.04</title>
      <link>https://xunyunliu.github.io/post/install_sogou/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 15:16:50 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xunyunliu.github.io/post/install_sogou/</guid>
      <description>Download download software package from here.
Preparation If the default language of your Ubuntu system is English, first install the required language support and make fcitx as your input method system.
if you like being more google-style, give google pinyin a try:
 sudo apt-get install fcitx-googlepinyin  Install  install the .deb with with the package manager, or using the following command.
sudo apt-get install ./sogoupinyin_2.1.0.0082_amd64.deb  Restart your computer to be able to see Sogou input in the text entry list</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install Matlab 2017b on Ubuntu 16.04</title>
      <link>https://xunyunliu.github.io/post/install_matlab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 14:51:08 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xunyunliu.github.io/post/install_matlab/</guid>
      <description>Download software Go to the download page and download the installation file as a zip.
You may have to log in using your matlab credentials before downloading the installation file.
Install  unzip the installation file to anywhere you like.
 open terminal, type the command below:
sudo sh install
 change any settings as you see fit and install the software to its preferred location /usr/local/MATLAB
 active MATLAB with your credentials</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something&#39;s wrong--perhaps a missing \item. \end{thebibliography}</title>
      <link>https://xunyunliu.github.io/post/latex1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 16:09:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xunyunliu.github.io/post/latex1/</guid>
      <description>When I compiled my manuscript for the first time, texstudio reports the following error message:
Something&#39;s wrong--perhaps a missing \item. \end{thebibliography}  I double checked the source code of the tex file but didn&amp;rsquo;t find anything unusual.
Soon I realised that I have deleted all the citations in the main content, and that is why the error message is triggered. So the solution is simple: add a citation from your library.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>